♪ soft piano music ♪
[Narrator] There is something very special about owning a home
It’s more than just four walls and a roof
But if those walls could talk
they’d tell you about all the adventures
you’ll start in them
(dog barks)
and the memories you’re going to make
More than just a place to live
a home is the place where life unfolds
It’s a place of many firsts
Like first meal in the new place
First steps
(child giggles)
First wheels (bicycle bell chimes)
And first independence
[Daughter] Yes!
(car door opens, engine starts)
(car horn honks)
[Narrator] First to leave the nest (dog whimpers)
and come back home again
(dog barks excitedly)
And if these walls could talk
they would definitely tell you how important it is to help protect your family
with Manulife’s mortgage protection insurance
It can help cover the mortgage payments
if something unexpected happens
Like an injury or illness (dog whimpers)
Or if one of you were no longer in the picture
It’s about more than just insurance
It’s about helping to make sure your loved ones are protected
Talk to your mortgage broker or lender about Manulife’s mortgage protection insurance